soundoflife.net 2011-06-06

# Privacy | Love Quotes and Sayings

This is the Privacy policy of soundoflife.net.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect and how we use it.

1) Visitor Information: For each visitor to our web site, our web server automatically recognizes information about your browser, IP address and your search term you used to come here (if you have reached the site from search engines). When you comment on the blog, you also provide your email address which is stored in our database.

The information we collect is used for internal review and used to improve the content of our web site, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

2) RSS Feeds: If you subscribe to our RSS feed with your email address, your email address will be saved at feedburner.com or feedblitz.com and we will have access to those email address. Those email addresses will be used only for sending the RSS feed from our web site. These email addresses will never be sold, disclosed or rented to any third party.

3) Cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

4) Ad servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies like Google (www.google.com/adsense) and kontera, that place ads on our web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies, with the help of cookies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of Google at http://www.google.com/privacy.html

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

*You can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at [Google’s Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

5) Contact: If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at soundoflife.netatgmaildotcom
